Alice Recknagel Ireys Papers, 1885-2001
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS
  - Education
    - Packer Collegiate Institute
      - Yearbook, "The Pelican"1931 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Cambridge School of Domestic Architecture and Landscape Architecture
      - General1931-86, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Alumnae Association1936-39 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Course notes, 1931-35
        - Architectural Construction 7a (Box 7, Folder 15-17)
        - Architectural Construction 7b (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
        - Architecture-Landscape 11: Professional Practice (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - Landscape Construction 7a (Box 8, Folder 5-8)
        - Landscape Construction 7b (Box 8, Folder 9-15)
        - Landscape Construction 7c (Box 8, Folder 16)
        - Landscape Construction 8c: Plant Materials (Box 8, Folder 17)
        - Unidentified (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
    - Junior League, Provisionals Course1936 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - General Design, A.H. Flanders1937 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - New York Chapter, American Society of Landscape Architects, Atelier: problemswinter 1938 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - "Class with Leo," grading1943 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified notessummer 1937 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Family
    - General1885-96 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Children: Anne French, Catherine Recknagel, and Henry Tillinghast IV1958-95(?), n.d. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Husband: Henry Tillinghast Ireys III1934, 1963-79, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Health1992, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Houses
    - 45 Willow Street, Brooklyn, NY1888-1994, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - "The Reckage," 802 Morraine St., Marshfield, MA1971-81, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 94 Carswell St., Green Harbor, MA1966-1979, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Memorabilia1920-95, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Radio interview: correspondence1997 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Silver Lake Camp1936-38 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - "The Living Landscapes of Alice Recknagel Ireys": video documentary
    - Correspondence1995-2000 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Notes1996-98 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Draft script and illustrations1996-97 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Filming schedules and outlines1996-97 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Videotape1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Volunteer activities1964-72 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- SERIES II. CLIENT FILES
  [Users of the client files must sign a written agreement to keep all names and street addresses of private clients confidential until January 1, 2031. The folder list is not included in the online version of the finding aid. Researchers may contact the Sophia Smith Collection for a copy.]
- SERIES III. FINANCIAL
  [Users of these financial records must sign a written agreement to keep all names and street addresses of private clients confidential until January 1, 2031]
  - General1928-92 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Cost estimates1940-41, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Lists of services and fees1938 and undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Invoices and notes1936-50, 1953-56, 1958, 1960-97, undated (Box 69, Folder 4-23)
  - Daily expense account books1937-41 (Box 69, Folder 24-25)
  - Account books
    - 1954-58 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - 1960s-89 (Box 70, Folder 1-3)
    - Inactive accounts1970s-90s (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Check ledgers1942-43 (Box 70, Folder 5-7)
- SERIES IV. MISCELLANEOUS PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES
  - Bulb orders1969-96, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Consultations
    - 1950-80 (Box 71, Folder 2-16)
    - 1981-98, undated (Box 72, Folder 1-7)
  - Exhibitions
    - General1937, 1981, undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - BeauxArch '86: The Architectural Exposition of the Hamptons1986 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Smith College Museum of Art, "Landscape Architects from the Cambridge School"1984 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Garden Tours1939, 1962, 1988-99 (Box 72, Folder 11-17)
  - Index to subject files (discarded 2003)undated (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Judging
    - Miscellaneous1961-62 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Garden Club of America, International Flower Show1961, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Long Island Nurseryman's Association, Greater Long Island Home Furnishings and Garden Show1965-67 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Massachusetts Horticultural Society, New England Spring Flower Show1988-90 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania Horticultural Society, Spring Flower Show1965, 1968, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Queens Botanic Garden, herb garden plans1969 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Sears Civic Beautification Contest1961 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Letterhead, business cardsundated (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Lists
    - Miscellaneous1983-92, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Telephone numbers1995-97 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Office, 101 Park Ave., Room 412: leases and subleases1939-41 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Office notescirca 1996, 1999, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Organizations
    - General1953-91 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - American Society of Landscape Architects
      - General1924-98, undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Council of Fellows1976-79 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - New York Chapter1938-94 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden
      - General1941-96, undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Horticultural Master Plan Committee1994-95, undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Planning Committee on the International Flower Show1960 (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - [Women's] Auxiliary1958-82 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn Brownstone Conference1983-86 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Brooklyn Heights Garden Club1962-92, undated (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Brownstone Revival Committee1972-75 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Garden Writers Association of America1964-92, undated (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Graham Home for Old Ladies Board of Managers1964-73 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Horticultural Alliance of the Hamptons1989-96, undated (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Horticultural Society of New York1992-94 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - W. Atlee Burpee Co., Horticultural Advisory Committee1987-89, undated (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Recommendations1978-92 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Weekly notes
    - 1971, 1975, Jan-Jun 1980 (Box 74, Folder 1-15)
    - Jul-Dec 1980, 1985, Jan-Jun 1990 (Box 75, Folder 1-12)
    - Jul-Dec 1990, 1995, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 1-11)
- SERIES V. PHOTOGRAPHS
  [Users of the photographs series must sign a written agreement to keep all names and street addresses of private clients confidential until January 1, 2031. Client names are not included in the online contents list for photographs. Researchers may contact the Sophia Smith Collection for a copy.]
  - Prints
    - Biographical
      - General1961-79, undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Alice Recknagel Ireys1962-92, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Alice Recknagel Ireys at job sites1970, 1992-97, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Family1981, 1997, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Client files
      [Contact SSC for more information]
      - Subjects
        - Approach/entranceundated (Box 89, Folder 1)
        - Birdsundated (Box 89, Folder 2)
        - Cityundated (Box 89, Folder 3)
        - Containersundated (Box 89, Folder 4)
        - Decksundated (Box 89, Folder 5)
        - Down hill siteundated (Box 89, Folder 6)
        - Fences and gatesundated (Box 89, Folder 7)
        - Flower gardensundated (Box 89, Folder 8)
        - Hedgesundated (Box 89, Folder 9)
        - Near the seaundated (Box 89, Folder 10)
        - Pathsundated (Box 89, Folder 11)
        - Planting at the houseundated (Box 89, Folder 12)
        - Plantsundated (Box 89, Folder 13-14)
        - Plants and designundated (Box 89, Folder 15)
        - Sculpturesundated (Box 89, Folder 16)
        - Seatsundated (Box 89, Folder 17)
        - Shadeundated (Box 89, Folder 18)
        - Stepsundated (Box 89, Folder 19)
        - Swimming poolsundated (Box 90, Folder 1-2)
        - Terraces/patiosundated (Box 90, Folder 3-4)
        - Up hill siteundated (Box 90, Folder 5)
        - Wallsundated (Box 90, Folder 6)
        - Waterundated (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Contact Sheets
        - 2 1/4 inch format, 1972, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 8-9)
        - 35 millimeter format, n.d (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Writings: general illustrations and gardens designed by others
        - How to Plan and Plant Your Own Property
          - Generalundated (Box 90, Folder 11)
          - Coffey, Claraundated (Box 90, Folder 12)
          - Coffin, Marianundated (Box 90, Folder 13)
          - Feil, Henryundated (Box 90, Folder 14)
          - Hayes propertyundated (Box 90, Folder 15)
          - Wilson, Helen Van Peltundated (Box 90, Folder 16)
        - Small Gardens for City and Country
          - Generalundated (Box 91, Folder 1-3)
          - Contact sheetsundated (Box 91, Folder 4)
          - Coffey, Claraundated (Box 91, Folder 5)
          - Coffin, Marianundated (Box 91, Folder 6)
          - Kennedy, Jamesundated (Box 91, Folder 7)
          - Langstaff gardenundated (Box 91, Folder 8)
          - Othmer gardenundated (Box 91, Folder 9)
          - Pearsall gardenundated (Box 91, Folder 10)
          - Rhoden gardenundated (Box 91, Folder 11)
          - Rullman gardenundated (Box 91, Folder 12)
          - Vadheim gardenundated (Box 91, Folder 13)
          - Unidentified
            - Pages 22-23undated (Box 91, Folder 14)
            - Pages 28 and 190undated (Box 91, Folder 15)
            - Pages 48-49 undated (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Slides
      - Biographical
        - General1959-80, undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
        - Alice Recknagel Ireys1983-88, undated (Box 92, Folder 2)
        - Travel1961-82 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Client files, [contact SSC for more information]
        - Subjects
          - Approach (Box 98, Folder 7)
          - Fences and gates (Box 98, Folder 8)
          - Flower gardens (Box 98, Folder 9)
          - Gazebos (Box 98, Folder 10)
          - Paths, steps, and walls (Box 98, Folder 11)
          - Plants (Box 98, Folder 12)
          - Pools and water features (Box 98, Folder 13)
          - Sculptures and features (Box 98, Folder 14)
          - Seats (Box 98, Folder 15)
          - Small and city gardens (Box 98, Folder 16)
          - Terraces (Box 98, Folder 17)
        - Teaching: Garden City, NY (Box 98, Folder 18)
        - Writings: "The Garden Life: James B.Cross of Long Island, New York" (Box 98, Folder 19)
      - Glass slides (Box 99, Folder 1-3)
      - Negatives (Box 100)
- SERIES VI. PROFESSIONAL CORRESPONDENCE
  - General
    - Miscellaneous1939-96, undated (Box 101, Folder 1-6)
    - Anderson, Dorothy May, 1976-81 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, James1979 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Salley, George1997, undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Galen1988-97, undated (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Horticulture Magazine1975-89, undated (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - License
    - New York Statecirca 1942-2000, undated (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - West Virginia State1981-97, undated (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Nurseries, contractors, and suppliers, [see also Client Files]
    - General1936, 1951-96 (Box 101, Folder 14-15)
    - Adolpho Corradi & Son/Corradi Landscape Associates1972-80 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Conard-Pyle Co./Star Roses1952-78 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Andre Viette Farm and Nursery1988-93 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Blackthorne Gardens1976-77 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Dutch Gardens1990-95 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Environmentals, Inc.1982-93, undated (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Frankenbach's Deerfield Nursery1972-94 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Henry M. Feil1961-80 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - John Scheepers, Inc.1972-97 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Keil Bros., Inc.1976-83, undated (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Martin Viette Nurseries1951-79, undated (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Mary Mattison van Schaik Imported Dutch Bulbs1963, 1971-90, undated (Box 102, Folder 12-15)
    - Nabel's Nurseries, Inc.1974-87, undated (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Oak Park Nurseries1951-53 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Oliver Nurseries, Inc. 1971-83 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Zandbergen Bros., Inc.1959-71, undated (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - Photographers
    - General1957-90 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - Adams, Molly1967-85, undated (Box 102, Folder 21)
  - Rogers Car Leasing1982-87, undated (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - Smith College1991-98 (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - Use of photographs1955-98 (Box 102, Folder 24)
- SERIES VII. SPEECHES
  - General correspondence1952-90, undated (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Lists of speeches1952-77, undated (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Speeches (chronological listing)
    - Radio Garden Club, "The Home Landscape: A Garden Plan"18 Feb 1938 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Garden City Garden Club, "Designing the Small Garden"11 Apr 1938 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Radio Garden Club, "For City Gardeners"10 May 1940 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Radio Garden Club, "Foundation Plantings: Design"29 Jan 1941 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Garden City Community Club, "Design of the Small Place"11 Apr 1945 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Shelter Island Garden Club, "Design of the Small Place"12 Aug 1945 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Westhampton, "The Green Garden"Dec 1948 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Federated Garden Clubs of Connecticut, Judging Course, "Things to Consider in Judging the Design of the Small Place"1948 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Flower Hill Garden Club, "Design of the Small Property"7 Mar 1949 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Little Garden Club, "Design of the Small Property"30 Mar 1949 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Irvington (NY) Garden Club, "Forms For Your Outdoor Living Area"19 Apr 1949 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Garden Club of America, Horticulture Committee7 Feb 1950 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Scarsdale Women's Club Garden Section, "Small Gardens"22 Oct 1952 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Ramapo Valley Garden Club, "Outdoor Living Areas"28 Oct 1952 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Schenectady Garden Club, "Outdoor Living Areas"18 Nov 1952 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Westhampton (NY) Garden Club, "Planning the Small Garden"3 Feb 1953 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - North Suffolk Garden Club, "Your Planning and Planting Problems"9 Jun 1953 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - North Suffolk Garden Club, "Berried Shrubs"13 Oct 1953 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Hortulus Garden Club, "The Green Garden"17 Oct 1953 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Caudatowa Garden Club (Ridgefield, CT), "Planning the Small Garden"circa 1954 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Brewster (MA) Garden Club, "Design of the Small Place"9 Mar 1954 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Schenectady Junior League Gardeners' Workshop, "Planning the Small Garden"2 Apr 1954 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Garden Circle of New Rochelle, "Replanning of the Old Garden or Designing and Planting a New One"6 Apr 1954 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Garden Club of the Oranges (NJ), "Garden Paths, Walls, and Terraces"9 Nov 1954 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Fairfield (CT) Garden Club, "Planning the Small Garden"1955 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Riverside (CT) Garden Club, "Planning the Small Garden"28 Feb 1955 (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - Ceres Garden Club of Rye (NY), "Landscaping Small Gardens and Terraces"12 Oct 1955 (Box 103, Folder 29)
    - Holly Society of America, 20th Annual Meeting, "Planting Holly in Small Garden Design"13 Apr 1956 (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - Manhattan Beach Garden Club, "Shrubs and Flowering Trees for the Small Garden"1 Feb 1957 (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Garden Club, speech and workshop "Planning the Small Garden"28-29 Mar and 1 Apr 1957 (Box 103, Folder 32)
    - Ramapo Valley Garden Club23 Apr 1957 (Box 103, Folder 33)
    - Plainfield (NJ) Garden Club, "Planning the Small Garden"19 Feb 1958 (Box 103, Folder 34)
    - Community Garden Club of Newburgh, "Planning the Small Garden"2 Apr 1958 (Box 103, Folder 35)
    - Federated Garden Clubs of Connecticut, "Landscape Design Workshop"25 Sep 1958 (Box 103, Folder 36)
    - Bartlett Tree Company Annual Meeting, Sep1959 (Box 103, Folder 37)
    - Henry Hicks Garden Club of the Westburys, "Planning the Small Garden"20 Mar 1961 (Box 103, Folder 38)
    - Nantucket Garden Club, "Planning the Small Garden"13 Sep 1961 (Box 103, Folder 39)
    - Matinecock Garden Club, "Evergreen Gardens"10 Oct 1961 (Box 103, Folder 40)
    - Green Fingers Garden Club, workshop16 Jan 1962 (Box 103, Folder 41)
    - Rye Garden Club, "Pruning"1 Feb 1962 (Box 103, Folder 42)
    - Williamsburg (VA) Garden Symposium, "Planning for Pleasure"20 Mar 1962 (Box 103, Folder 43)
    - Longwood Gardens, "Planting the Small Place"28 Mar 1962 (Box 103, Folder 44)
    - North County Garden Club of Long Island, "Low and Slow Growing Evergreens"9 Apr 1962 (Box 103, Folder 45)
    - Forest Garden Club (MD), "Planning the Small Garden"17 Apr 1962 (Box 103, Folder 46)
    - Garden Club of Lawrence, "Planning a Garden Pool Using Unusual Dwarf Material"7 Aug 1962 (Box 103, Folder 47)
    - Garden Club of Yorktown, "Planning the Small Garden"8 Aug 1962 (Box 103, Folder 48)
    - Short Hills Garden Club16 Jan 1963 (Box 103, Folder 49)
    - Federated Garden Clubs of America, Third District, workshop28 Jan 1963 (Box 103, Folder 50)
    - West Hartford (CT) Garden Club, "Planning the Small Place"13 Mar 1963 (Box 103, Folder 51)
    - Englewood (NJ) Arbor Day Ceremony27 Apr 1963 (Box 103, Folder 52)
    - Lake George Garden Club, "Planning Small Gardens"17 Jul 1963 (Box 103, Folder 53)
    - Westhampton (NY) Garden Club, "Planting a Sea Shore Garden"23 Jul 1963 (Box 103, Folder 54)
    - Sasqua Garden Club, "Planning the Small Garden"17 Sep 1963 (Box 103, Folder 55)
    - Van Rensselaer Garden Club, workshop "General Planning," and "Detail Planning"24 Oct 1963 (Box 103, Folder 56)
    - Staten Island Garden Club, "Planning Small Gardens"22 Jan 1964 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Garden Club of Lawrence, "Pruning"4 May 1964 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Millbrook (NY) Garden Club16 Jul 1964 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Martha's Vineyard Garden Club, "Outdoor Living Areas"28 Jul 1964 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Hillside Garden Club, Lynchburg, VA, "The Design of Small Gardens"14 Oct 1964 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Rye Garden Club, "Gardening With Containers"1 Dec 1964 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Garden Club of Wilmington (DE), "Planning the Small Garden with Broad-Leafed Evergreens"11 Jan 1965 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - North Country Garden Club, "Planning the Small Garden with Broad-Leafed Evergreens"10 Feb 1965 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Essex Garden Club, "Planning the Small Garden"1 Mar 1965 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Richmond (NY) Garden Club, "Planning the Home Grounds"8 Apr 1965 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Mystic (CT) Garden Club, "Planning with Evergreens for the Small Garden"28 Sep 1965 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Garden Club Civic Conference, Washington, DC, "Community Projects: Planning and Planting"27 Oct 1965 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Garden Club of Montclair, "Landscape Ideas for Old and New Properties"17 Jan 1966 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Stony Brook Garden Club of Princeton, "Plant Identification and Use"17 Jan? 1966 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Rolling Hills Garden Club, "Unusual Evergreens to Use in Your Garden"21 Jan 1966 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - North Country Garden Club of Long Island, "Color Throughout the Year"2 Mar 1966 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - West Virginia Garden Club Annual Meeting, "Community Projects: Planning and Planting"29 Mar 1966 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Three Harbors Garden Club, "Unusual Plant Material for the Small Garden"4 Apr 1966 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Matinecock Garden Club12 Apr 1966 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Rumson (NJ) Garden Club, "Planning with Evergreens for the Small Garden"19 Apr 1966 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - New Canaan (CT) Garden Club, "Planning with Evergreens for the Small Garden"10 Aug 1966 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Garden Club of Lawrence, "The Ericaceae Family"7 Nov 1966 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Garden Club of Lawrence, "Flowering Shrubs and Ground Covers"9 Jan 1967 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Garden Club of Danville (VA), "Effective Garden Design"3 Feb 1967 (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - Green Acres Garden Club (Armonk, NY), "Design of Home Grounds"12 Apr 1967 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden Women's Auxiliary, "Community Projects--Planning and Planting for: Your City-Your Street-You!"4 May 1967 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Garden Club of Shelter Island, "Planting the Small Garden"30 Aug 1967 (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - Scarsdale Audubon Society, "Planting to Attract Birds"8 Feb 1968 (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - Scarsdale Garden Club, "Planning Your Outdoor Living Areas"28 Mar 1968 (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - Martha's Vineyard Garden Club, "Seashore Planning and Planting"9 Jul 1968 (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - Garden Club of America, northeastern zone meeting, "Landscape Planning for Private and Public Areas"2 Oct 1968 (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - South Side Garden Club of Long Island, "Planning Your Home Property"18 Nov 1968 (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - Rusticus Garden Club (Bedford, NY)14 Jan 1969 (Box 104, Folder 33)
    - James River Garden Club (Richmond, VA), "Design of the Home Property"12 Feb 1969 (Box 104, Folder 34)
    - Wilton Garden Club, "Design of the Home Property"10 Mar 1969 (Box 104, Folder 35)
    - Matinecock Garden Club (Long Island), "Bulb Planting for an Evergreen Garden"9 Sep 1969 (Box 104, Folder 36)
    - Garden Club of Irvington (NY), "The Design of Small Gardens"23 Sep 1969 (Box 104, Folder 37)
    - Milton Garden Club, "The Design of Small Gardens"20 Oct 1969 (Box 104, Folder 38)
    - Garden Club of Darien (CT), "Planning the Small Property"21 Oct 1969 (Box 104, Folder 39)
    - Garden Club of Michigan, "Planning Small Gardens"12 Nov 1969 (Box 104, Folder 40)
    - Federated Garden Clubs of New York, 7th District, "Design of the Home Property"8 Apr 1970 (Box 104, Folder 41)
    - Acorn Garden Club (Washington, DC), "The Design of Small Gardens"9 Nov 1970 (Box 104, Folder 42)
    - Rock Spring Garden Club (Arlington, VA)21 Jan 1971 (Box 104, Folder 43)
    - Farmington House and Garden Symposium (Louisville, KY), "Landscape Design Today"3 Feb 1971 (Box 104, Folder 44)
    - Jupiter Island Garden Club (Hobe Sound, FL), "Planning Small Gardens"16 Feb 1971 (Box 104, Folder 45)
    - Garden Club of Morristown (NJ), "The Design of Small Gardens"17 Mar 1971 (Box 104, Folder 46)
    - Garden Club of Madison (CT), "Design of the Home Property"10 Aug 1971 (Box 104, Folder 47)
    - Shippon Point Garden Club, "Design of the Home Property"23 Sep 1971 (Box 104, Folder 48)
    - Brooklyn Heights Garden Club, "Planting for City Gardens and Gardening with Containers"10 Jan 1972 (Box 104, Folder 49)
    - Green Fingers Garden Club (Greenwich, CT), "Landscaping a Small Property"11 Jan 1972 (Box 104, Folder 50)
    - Federated Garden Clubs of New York State, "Design for Easy Maintenance"17 Jan 1972 (Box 104, Folder 51)
    - American Rhododendron Society, "Landscape Planning with Rhododendrons and Azaleas"16 Mar 1972 (Box 104, Folder 52)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden, Clark Memorial Garden, "Planning a Bulb Garden"16 Aug 1972 (Box 104, Folder 53)
    - Bryant Park Flower Show, "Planning a Small Garden"6 Oct 1972 (Box 104, Folder 54)
    - Hillside Garden Club (Lynchburg, VA), "What's New in Garden Planning"11 Oct 1972 (Box 104, Folder 55)
    - Rake and Hoe Garden Club (Westfield, NJ), "Design of the Home Property"17 Jan 1973 (Box 104, Folder 56)
    - Garden Club of New Haven (CT), "Planning the Small Property"5 Feb 1973 (Box 104, Folder 57)
    - Lake and Valley Garden Club (Cooperstown, NY), "The Design of Small Gardens"5 Sep 1973 (Box 104, Folder 58)
    - Garden City (NY) Community Club, "Landscaping the Small Property"8 Feb 1974 (Box 104, Folder 59)
    - Garden Club of Montclair (NJ), "Designing the Small Property"22 Apr 1974 (Box 104, Folder 60)
    - Scarsdale Sunday Recreation Program, "Planning Your Garden Now for Spring"12 Jan 1975 (Box 104, Folder 61)
    - Mrs. Field's Literary Club16 Jan 1975 (Box 104, Folder 62)